Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1985-037
  - Food Research Institute, 10/80-6/1982; AA 4.8 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.8)
  - Hoover Institute, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.9 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Ctr. for Res. in International Studies, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.10 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.10)
  - Japanese Studies at Stanford, 1/76-2/1981; AA 4.10.2 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.10.2)
  - rogram on US-China Relations, 9/1981-7/1981; AA 4.10.3 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.10.3)
  - Middle Eastern Studies Prog. at SU, 10/80-9/1981; AA 4.10.5 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.10.5)
  - Libraries, 12/80-8/1982; AA 4.12 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.12)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 9/1981-7/1982; AA 4.13 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.13)
  - School of Law, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.15 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.15)
  - Research Animal Facility, 2/1982-3/1982; AA 4.17.6 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.17.6)
  - ChiIdren's Hospital/Health Council, 8/1979-6/1982; AA 4.17.7 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.17.7)
  - Ctr. for Information Technology, 10/1981-3/1982; AA 4.22 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.22)
  - Awards and Prizes, 10/78-5/1982; AA 5 (Box 11, Folder AA 5)
  - Fellowships, Misc./General, 4/80-1/1982; AA 8.0 (Box 11, Folder AA 8.0)
  - Miriam and John Marble Fellowship, 26573; AA 8.26 (Box 11, Folder AA 8.26)
  - Harry Camp Memorial Lectures, 10/78-10/1979; AA 9.7 (Box 11, Folder AA 9.7)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Misc., 10/1981-6/1982; AA 10.0 (Box 11, Folder AA 10.0)
  - Proposed Professorships, 4/72-7/1982; AA 10.1 (Box 11, Folder AA 10.1)
  - ASSU Professorship, 9/76-5/1981; AA 10.2 (Box 11, Folder AA 10.2)
  - Adjunct Professoriate, 1/76-8/1982; AA 10.3 (Box 11, Folder AA 10.3)
  - Soc. for Indstr. and Appld. Mathematics, 2/1979-10/1979; O 8.57 (Box 11, Folder O 8.57)
  - Michigan University, 6/1979-4/1980; O 8.47 (Box 11, Folder O 8.47)
  - Brown University, 8/1979-3/1980; O 8.13 (Box 11, Folder O 8.13)
  - Brigham Young University, 3/1979-11/1979; O 8.12 (Box 11, Folder O 8.12)
  - Women at Stanford, 6/1981-6/1982; AD 9.5 (Box 11, Folder AD 9.5)
  - Minority Enrollment, 5/1979-7/1981; AD 8.21.2 (Box 11, Folder AD 8.21.2)
  - California Institute of Technology, 2/1979-3/1981; O 8.16 (Box 11, Folder O 8.16)
  - Margaret Jacks Prof. in Education, 2/70-11/71; AA 10.29 (Box 11, Folder AA 10.29)
  - Aaron-Roland Lectures, 4/78-5/78; AA 9.3 (Box 11, Folder AA 9.3)
  - Sloss Visiting Lectureship, 3/77-4/78; AA 9.18 (Box 11, Folder AA 9.18)
  - Raymond Fred West Memorial Lectures, 3/73-3/1982; AA 9.20 (Box 11, Folder AA 9.20)
  - Haas-Sloss Lectures, 6/75-4/78; AA 9.12 (Box 11, Folder AA 9.12)
  - National Science Foundation Fellows, 3/72-11/1979; AA 8.34 (Box 11, Folder AA 8.34)
  - Donald L. Stilwell, 29618; AA 4.6/2 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.6/2)
  - Research Assistants, 7/67-6/77; R 1.8.1 (Box 11, Folder R 1.8.1)
  - ASSU: Freshmen Intern Program, 7/71-12/1979; ST 2.7.1 (Box 11, Folder ST 2.7.1)
  - New Founder's League, 4/1979-5/1980; AL 4.4 (Box 11, Folder AL 4.4)
  - Buck Club, 1/1979-5/1982; AL 4.1 (Box 11, Folder AL 4.1)
  - Computation Center, 6/73-5/78; AA 4.16 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.16)
  - Pre-Med Advising, 2/1979-1/1982; AA 3.7.1 (Box 11, Folder AA 3.7.1)
  - Shockley, William, 29373; AA 2.6.2/2 (Box 11, Folder AA 2.6.2/2)
  - SUH DOD: Community Physicians Issue, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.17.3 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.17.3)
  - Financial Aids, 9/1981-8/1982; AD 8.12 (Box 11, Folder AD 8.12)
  - Prospective Donors, 9/1981-8/1982; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - Research Libraries Group, 9/1981-12/1981; AA 4.12.1 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.12.1)
  - Hospital Modernization Project, 9/1981-3/1982; AA 4.17.5 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.17.5)
  - Foundations, Funds, Misc., 11/1981-8/1982; AD 12.10.4 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 4/1982-8/1982; AD 8.18 (Box 11, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 9/1981-8/1982; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.14.7/64)
  - Jake Gimbel Sex Psychology Lectures, 5/71-2/1979; AA 9.10 (Box 11, Folder AA 9.10)
  - Board of Trustees, 6/1982-8/1982; B1 (Box 11, Folder B1)
  - School of Medicine, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.6 (Box 11, Folder AA 4.6)
  - Office of Development, 9/1981-8/1982; AD 12.10.1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Jake Gimbel Athletic Attitude Prize, 5/73-5/1982; AA 5.24 (Box 12, Folder AA 5.24)
  - SUH Board Of Directors, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.17.2 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - H. Bruce Franklin, 1980; AA 2.6.2/1 (Box 12, Folder AA 2.6.2/1)
  - Ctr. for Integrated Systems Dev., 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.4.19 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.4.19)
  - Admissions, 10/1981-8/1982; AD 8.1.2 (Box 12, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - Hospital Modernization Project, 4/1982-8/1982; AA 4.17.5 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.17.5)
  - Medical Center/Hospital, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.17 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Hammer and Coffin Fund, 29342; AD 12.10.4/84 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/84)
  - Fairleigh S. Dickinson, Jr., 7/1979-3/1981; AD 12.10.3/5-17 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-17)
  - Budgets, 8/1981-12/1981; AD 12.5 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Dept of Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 3/1981-7/1982; AA 4.1.30 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 9/1981-3/1982; AD 8.18 1 (Box 12, Folder AD 8.18 1)
  - Djerassi Foundation, 3/1979-10/1979; AD 12.10.4/57 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/57)
  - Research Libraries Group, 1/1982-8/1982; AA 4.12.1 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.12.1)
  - Administrative Council, 9/1981-1/1982; AD 4.12 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/1981-5/1982; B1 (Box 12, Folder B1)
  - Provost's Cttee. for Jasper Ridge, 4/74-8/76; AD 12 14.7/43 (Box 12, Folder AD 12 14.7/43)
  - Budgets, 9/80-4/1982; PAD 12.5 (Box 12, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Provost's Cttee. for Jasper Ridge, 8/76-8/1979; AD 12.14.7/43 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.14.7/43)
  - Provost's Cttee. for Jasper Ridge, 3/76-6/1982; AD 12.4.7/43 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.4.7/43)
  - California State Government, 9/1981-2/1982; G 1.2 (Box 12, Folder G 1.2)
  - CA Educational Facilities Authority, 3/1979-4/1982; G 1.3.2 (Box 12, Folder G 1.3.2)
  - CA Postsecondary Education Commission, 3/1979-2/1982; G 1.3.5 (Box 12, Folder G 1.3.5)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 10/1979-1/1980; G 2.3 (Box 12, Folder G 2.3)
  - U.S. Government Relations, 1/1982-8/1982; G 3 (Box 12, Folder G 3)
  - Federal Legislation, 2/1981-8/1982; G 3.1 (Box 12, Folder G 3.1)
  - Department of Defense (DOD), 5/1979-5/1982; G 3.7 (Box 12, Folder G 3.7)
  - Security Guide: Dept. of Defense, 4/1979-5/1980; G 3.7.5 (Box 12, Folder G 3.7.5)
  - International Traffic in Arms Regula., 29983; G 3.7.6 (Box 12, Folder G 3.7.6)
  - International Traffic in Arms Regula., 9/1981-1/1982; G 3.7.6 (Box 12, Folder G 3.7.6)
  - Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare, 7/1979-12/1981; G 3.8 (Box 12, Folder G 3.8)
  - National Institute of Health, 11/80-8/1982; G 3.8.2 (Box 12, Folder G 3.8.2)
  - Department of Education, 9/80-3/1981; G 3.8.3 (Box 12, Folder G 3.8.3)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 12/1979-2/1981; G 3.12.1 (Box 12, Folder G 3.12.1)
  - Internl. Research and Exchange, 5/1979-6/1982; G 3.16.6 (Box 12, Folder G 3.16.6)
  - National Science Foundation, 7/80-6/1981; G 3.19 (Box 12, Folder G 3.19)
  - National Medal of Science, 9/1979-1/1980; G 3.19.11 (Box 12, Folder G 3.19.11)
  - Educom, 1/1979-1/1982; G 3.19.12 (Box 12, Folder G 3.19.12)
  - Federal Funding for Higher Education, 1/1979-6/1981; G 3.21 (Box 12, Folder G 3.21)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 4/1979-2/1982; G 3.27 (Box 12, Folder G 3.27)
  - Federal Agencies, Misc., 3/1979-6/1981; G 3.29 (Box 12, Folder G 3.29)
  - Palo Alto, City of: Community Relations, 10/80-8/1982; G 4.2 (Box 12, Folder G 4.2)
  - Stanford/Palo Alto Liaison Committee, 8/1979-5/1980; G 4.2.1 (Box 12, Folder G 4.2.1)
  - Santa Clara County, 1/1981-8/1982; G 4.6 (Box 12, Folder G 4.6)
  - Foreign Countries, Govts., Misc., 9/80-6/1982; G 5 (Box 12, Folder G 5)
  - China, 10/1981-6/1982; G 5^2 (Box 12, Folder G 5^2)
  - Alumni Relations, 1/1979-8/1982; AL 1 (Box 12, Folder AL 1)
  - Alumni Association, 9/80-7/1982; AL 3 (Box 12, Folder AL 3)
  - Alumni College, 9/80-7/1982; AL 1.6 (Box 12, Folder AL 1.6)
  - Alumni Conferences, 11/80-8/1982; AL 1.7 (Box 12, Folder AL 1.7)
  - Stanford Magazine, 10/80-11/1981; AL 1.12 (Box 12, Folder AL 1.12)
  - Alumni Association, 4/80-7/1982; AL 3 (Box 12, Folder AL 3)
  - Alum. Exec. Bd. and Advisory Council, 2/1979-5/1982; AL 3.1 (Box 12, Folder AL 3.1)
  - Alumni Club of Los Angeles, 2/1979-5/1982; AL 3.4.6 (Box 12, Folder AL 3.4.6)
  - Other Alumni Groups, Misc., 1/1979-2/1981; AL 4 (Box 12, Folder AL 4)
  - Students, Misc., 9/1981-8/1982; ST 1 (Box 12, Folder ST 1)
  - ASSU, General, 6/1982-8/1982; ST 2 (Box 12, Folder ST 2)
  - ASSU, General, 11/1979-6/1982; ST 2 (Box 12, Folder ST 2)
  - ASSU Cttee. on Nominations, 9/80-7/1982; ST 2.7 (Box 12, Folder ST 2.7)
  - Stanford Band, 9/1981-12/1981; ST 3.4 (Box 12, Folder ST 3.4)
  - KZSU, 2/1981-4/1982; ST 3.18 (Box 12, Folder ST 3.18)
  - Chaparral, 2/80-4/1981; ST 3.23.5 (Box 12, Folder ST 3.23.5)
  - Stanford Daily, 3/80-4/1982; ST 3.23.7 (Box 12, Folder ST 3.23.7)
  - SWOPSI, 6/1979-6/1980; 3.28 (Box 12, Folder 3.28)
  - SCIRE, 1/80-6/1982; ST 3.30 (Box 12, Folder ST 3.30)
  - Student Deaths, 10/1979-11/1981; ST 5.2 (Box 12, Folder ST 5.2)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford, 5/80-4/1981; ST 4.2 (Box 12, Folder ST 4.2)
  - ARLO: Action Research Liasion Office, 5/80-5/1982; ST 4.1 (Box 12, Folder ST 4.1)
  - BOT By-Laws, 1/74-4/1980; B 7 (Box 12, Folder B 7)
  - Finance and Development Committee, 11/1981-6/1982; B 14.4 (Box 12, Folder B 14.4)
  - Trustee Investment Committee, 11/1981-2/1982; B 14.5 (Box 12, Folder B 14.5)
  - Trustee Cttee. on Land and Bldgs. (Plng.), 2/1979-12/1981; B 14.6 (Box 14, Folder B 14.6)
  - Cttee. on Nominations, 6/80-10/1981; B 14.7 (Box 14, Folder B 14.7)
  - Ad Hoc Cttee. on the Medical Center, 9/80-10/1980; B 14.9 (Box 14, Folder B 14.9)
  - Boys Town Center, 1/1981-8/1982; O 1.10 (Box 14, Folder O 1.10)
  - Cable Television, 11/80-6/1982; O 1.39 (Box 14, Folder O 1.39)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed., 9/1981-8/1982; O 3.1 (Box 14, Folder O 3.1)
  - PAC-10, 12/1981-8/1982; O 3.47 (Box 14, Folder O 3.47)
  - PAC-10, 9/1981-11/1981; 0 3.47 (Box 14, Folder 0 3.47)
  - Assn. ssn. of American Medical Colleges, 2/80-11/1981; O 5.1 (Box 14, Folder O 5.1)
  - Assn. of American Universities, 7/1982-8/1982; O 8.7 (Box 14, Folder O 8.7)
  - Assn. of American Universities, 9/1981-6/1982; O 8.7 (Box 14, Folder O 8.7)
  - Seven Universities, 4/1979-4/1981; O 8.39 (Box 14, Folder O 8.39)
  - Western Assn. of Schools and Colleges, 9/1981-3/1982; O 8.52 (Box 14, Folder O 8.52)
  - Research, Misc., 9/1981-8/1982; O (Box 14, Folder O)
  - Vice Provost for Research, 7/1981-8/1982; R 1.1 (Box 14, Folder R 1.1)
  - Committee on Research, 11/8l-4/1982; R 1.2 (Box 14, Folder R 1.2)
  - Center for Research on Women, 10/80-6/1982; R 1.8 (Box 14, Folder R 1.8)
  - Stanford Synchrotron Radiation Lab, 10/1981-8/1982; R 1.9 (Box 14, Folder R 1.9)
  - University-Industry Relations, General, 11/1981-6/1982; R 2.2 (Box 14, Folder R 2.2)
  - Research Policies, 11/1981-8/1982; R 2.0 (Box 14, Folder R 2.0)
  - Inst. Support for Research, Misc., 5/1979-1/1982; R 3 (Box 14, Folder R 3)
  - Indirect Costs, 9/1981-5/1982; R 3.1 (Box 14, Folder R 3.1)
  - Senate of the Acad. Cncl. Corresp., 4/80-7/1982; C 2.1 (Box 14, Folder C 2.1)
  - Advisory Board, 9/1981-6/1982; C 3.0 (Box 14, Folder C 3.0)
  - Cttee. on Cttees. Correspondence, 1/1979-4/1980; C 4.21 (Box 14, Folder C 4.21)
  - Committee of the Academic Council, 1/1979-5/1981; C 5 (Box 14, Folder C 5)
  - Cttee. on Acad. Appraisal and Achievement, 10/1979-6/1981; C 5.1 (Box 14, Folder C 5.1)
  - Sub-Cttee. on Eval. of Teaching, 4/80-8/1982; C 5.1.2 (Box 14, Folder C 5.1.2)
  - Gores and Dinkelspiel Awards, 6/1981-5/1982; C 5.1.3 (Box 14, Folder C 5.1.3)
  - The Rhodes-Marshall Scholarship Panel, 7/80-9/1981; C 5.1.4 (Box 14, Folder C 5.1.4)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs, 1/1979-5/1979; C 5.2 (Box 14, Folder C 5.2)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 11/80-6/1982; C 5.3 (Box 14, Folder C 5.3)
  - Committee on Libraries, 10/80-2/1982; C 5.4 (Box 14, Folder C 5.4)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 5.7; C (Box 14, Folder C)
  - Undergraduate Cabinet, 3/1981-6/1982; C 5.7.1 (Box 15, Folder C 5.7.1)
  - Universities Committees, 10/77-6/1982; C 6 (Box 15, Folder C 6)
  - Cttee. on Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 6/78-10/1981; C 6.1 (Box 15, Folder C 6.1)
  - Faculty and Staff Benefits Cttee., 10/80-1/1982; C 6.5 (Box 15, Folder C 6.5)
  - Cttee. on Land and Building Development, 9/1981-8/1982; C 6.6 (Box 15, Folder C 6.6)
  - Panel and Sub-Cttee. on Outdoor Sculpture, 1/1979-5/1982; C 6.6.2 (Box 15, Folder C 6.6.2)
  - Cttee. on Earthquake Preparedness, 10/1981-6/1982; C 6.7 (Box 15, Folder C 6.7)
  - Cttee. on Public Events, 11/80-6/1982; C 6.8 (Box 15, Folder C 6.8)
  - Cttee. on Services to Students, 1/1982-5/1982; C 6.9 (Box 15, Folder C 6.9)
  - Cttee. on Affirm. Action in Employment, 12/80-8/1982; C 6.10 (Box 15, Folder C 6.10)
  - Cttee. on Investment Responsibility, 9/8l-7/1982; C 7.7 (Box 15, Folder C 7.7)
  - Univ. Advisory Cttee. on Budget Plng., 11/1981-5/1982; C 7.13 (Box 15, Folder C 7.13)
  - Cttee. on Parking and Transportation, 9/1981-12/1981; C 8.1 (Box 15, Folder C 8.1)
  - Radiological Hazards Control Cttee., 10/80-6/1982; C 8.2 (Box 15, Folder C 8.2)
  - SLAC Coordinating Committee, 11/1979-1/1982; C 8.4 (Box 15, Folder C 8.4)
  - SLAC Scientific Policy Committee, 1/1982-8/1982; C 8.4.1 (Box 15, Folder C 8.4.1)
  - University Library Council, 9/80-6/1982; C 8.5 (Box 15, Folder C 8.5)
  - Panel on the University Press, 4/80-6/1982; C 8.6 (Box 15, Folder C 8.6)
  - Administrative Panel on Human Subjects, 9/80-4/1982; C 8.7 (Box 15, Folder C 8.7)
  - Ad. Panel on Recombinant DNA Molecules, 10/80-9/1981; C 8.8 (Box 15, Folder C 8.8)
  - Ad. Panel on Health and Safety, 9/1981-7/1982; C 8.10 (Box 15, Folder C 8.10)
  - Ad. Panel on Laboratory Animal Care, 9/80-3/1982; C 8.11 (Box 15, Folder C 8.11)
  - Ad. Panel on Internal Affirm. Action, 11/80-11/1981; C 8.12 (Box 15, Folder C 8.12)
  - Ad. Panel on External Affirm. Action, 8/80-7/1982; C 8.13 (Box 15, Folder C 8.13)
  - Stanford Judicial Council, 6/1982-7/1982; C 9.4 (Box 15, Folder C 9.4)
  - Honor Code Commission, 6/1981-6/1982; C 9.5 (Box 15, Folder C 9.5)
  - Ad. Panel on Privacy of Information, 1/80-8/1982; C 11 (Box 15, Folder C 11)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1986-088
  - Dean's Council Agenda file #3, 1/1982-5/1983; PAA 1.51 (Box 1, Folder PAA 1.51)
  - Emeriti, 1983; PAA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder PAA 2.2)
  - Franklin, Prof. H. Bruce Case, 1971-1986; AA 2.6.2/1 (Box 1, Folder AA 2.6.2/1)
  - Fellows of the University, 1/1981-6/1983; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder AA 2.9)
  - Stanford Center for Information Tech., 9/1982-12/1982; PAA 4.22 (Box 1, Folder PAA 4.22)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/1982-8/1983; PAA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder PAA 4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/80-6/1983; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1)
  - Biological Sciences, 6/80-7/1983; AA 4.1.2 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.2)
  - Communication Dept., 9/1982-8/1983; PAA 4.1.15 (Box 1, Folder PAA 4.1.15)
  - Center for Economic Policy Research, 1980-6/1984; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.20/1)
  - Human Biology, 1980-8/1983; AA 4.1.26 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.26)
  - Human Biology, 9/1982-8/1983; PAA 4.1.26 (Box 1, Folder PAA 4.1.26)
  - Dept. of Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 9/1983-12/1983; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Dept. of Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 3/1983-8/1983; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Dept. of Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 9/1982-2/1983; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Dept. of Athletics-Budget, 12/80-5/1982; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Dept. of Athletics, 9/1981-8/1983; PAA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder PAA 4.1.30)
  - Ctr. For Integrated Systems Develop., 9/1982-12/1983; PAA 4.4.19 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.4.19)
  - Ctr. For Integrated Systems Develop., 9/1982-8/1983; AA 4.4.19 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.4.19)
  - School of Education, 8/1981-8/1983; PAA 4.5 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.5)
  - Medical School, 9/1982-1/1983; PAA 4.6 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - Medical School, 2/1983-8/1983; PAA 4.6 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 9/1982-8/1983; AA 4.6 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 9/1983-8/1984; AA 4.6 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.6)
  - Executive Committee, Medical School, 1/1982-8/1983; PAA 4.6.3 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.6.3)
  - Committee on Human Nutrition, 1978-9/1983; PAA 4.8 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.8)
  - Hoover Institution, 3/1983-8/83, 9/1982-2/1983; AA 4.9 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Hoover/Stanford Relationship, 4/1983-12/1983; AA 4.9.1 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.9.1)
  - Center for Research in International Studies, 5/1983-8/1983; AA 4.10 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.10)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament, 9/1981-8/1982; AA 4.10.1 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.10.1)
  - Libraries, 9/1982-8/1983; AA 4.12 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.12)
  - Libraries, 9/80-8/1983; PAA 4.12 (Box 2, Folder PAA 4.12)
  - Research Libraries Group, 9/1982-12/1982; AA 4.12.1 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.12.1)
  - Stanford Mascot/Symbol, 3/72-12/75; AD 2.7 (Box 3, Folder AD 2.7)
  - Stanford Mascot/Symbol, 1976-1978; AD 2.7 (Box 3, Folder AD 2.7)
  - Stanford Mascot/Symbol, 1979; AD 2.7 (Box 3, Folder AD 2.7)
  - Stanford Mascot/Symbol, 1980-82; AD 2.7 (Box 3, Folder AD 2.7)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 12/1981-12/1983; PAD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 12/1982-4/1983; PAD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 5/1983-7/1983; PAD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 8/1983-10/1983; PAD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 30651; PAD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 5/1982-1/1983; AD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 2/1983-5/1983; AD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 5/1983-6/1983; AD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 7/1983-12/1983; AD 4.12 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.12)
  - SU Hospital, 12/1981-8/1982; AA 4.17 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital, 9/1982-8/1983; AA 4.17 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital (Report), 30651; AA 4.17 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital, 1980, 9/1982-3/1983; AA 4.17 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital, 4/1983-8/1983; AA 4.17 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital Board of Directors, 1/1982-1/1983; AA 4.17.2 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - SU Hospital Board of Directors, 2/1983-11/1983; AA 4.17.2 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - SU Hospital Board of Directors, 9/1983-12/1983; AA 4.17.2 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - SU Hospital Board of Directors, Community Physicians Issue, 9/1982-8/1983; AA 4.17.3 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17.3)
  - Hospital Modernization Project, 1981, 8/1982-8/1983; AA 4.17.5 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17.5)
  - Center for Information Technology, 10/1981-8/1982; PAA 4.22 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.22)
  - Center for Information Technology, 9/1982-12/1982; PAA 4.22 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.22)
  - Center for Information Technology, 9/1982-8/1983; PAA 4.22 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.22)
  - Dean of Students, Case #s Discipline, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 7.2.5 (Box 5, Folder AD 7.2.5)
  - Admissions, 1982; AD 8.1.2 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - SU Overseas Studies, 6/1982-8/1983; PAD 8.11 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.11)
  - Financial Aids, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 8.12 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.12)
  - Study Group on Financial Aids, 1983; AD 8.12 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.12)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 4/1983-8/1983; AD 8.18 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 9/1982-3/1983; AD 8.18 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 9/1982-8/1983; PAD 8.18 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Housing: Stanford West, 3/1981-9/1983; PAD 8.18 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Fraternities and Sororities (Report), 30498; AD 8.18.8 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18.8)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 8.18.8 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18.8)
  - Housing Students, 9/1982-8/1984; AD 8.18.11 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18.11)
  - Housing Students, 9/1982-9/1983; PAD 8.18.11 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18.11)
  - Residential Education, 1/80-8/1982; AD 8.18.13 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18.13)
  - Chicano Affairs, 9/1981-12/1983; AD 9.2 (Box 5, Folder AD 9.2)
  - Chicano Affairs, 1981-8/1983; PAD 9.2 (Box 5, Folder PAD 9.2)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 1982-8/1983; AD 9.6 (Box 5, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program (Report), 30042; AD 9.6 (Box 5, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/1982-8/1983; PAD 9.6 (Box 5, Folder PAD 9.6)
  - Endowed Chairs, Professorships, 9/1982-8/1983; PAA 10 (Box 6, Folder PAA 10)
  - Management Development Program, 9/80-8/1983; PAD 10.2 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10.2)
  - Self Study, 7/1982-8/1983; AD 10.3 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.3)
  - Self Study, 9/1982-12-82; PAD 10.3 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10.3)
  - United Stanford Employees, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 10.7.8 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.7.8)
  - Personnel Policies/Hiring Practices, PAD 10.8 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10.8)
  - Faculty/Staff Fringe Benefits, 9/1982-8/1983; PAD 10.8.9 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10.8.9)
  - Grievance Cases, 6/1981-4/1983; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievance Cases, 5/1983-8/1983; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievance Cases, 9/1982-4/1983; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievances-Goffney, 1981-1983; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10.8.10/1)
  - TIAA/CREF and Prudential, 5/1982-9/1983; AD 10.8.17/3 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.8.17/3)
  - Salaries, 11/80-6/1983; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10.8.19)
  - Tuition Scholarship, 6/1982-12/1982; AD 10.8.22 (Box 6, Folder AD 10.8.22)
  - Commencement, 1984; AD 11.7.2 (Box 6, Folder AD 11.7.2)
  - SU Press, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 11.8.9 (Box 6, Folder AD 11.8.9)
  - Business and Finance, 8/1982-9/1983; PAD 12.2 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.2)
  - Business and Finance, 9/1981-1983; AD 12.2 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.2)
  - SU Investment Management, 4/1983-11/1983; AD 12.3.1 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.3.1)
  - Auditing, 12/1982-8/1983; PAD 12.4 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.4)
  - Budgets, 6/1979-11/1982; PAD 12.5 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 12/1982-8/1983; PAD 12.5 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Budget-Facilities Plan and Funding Forecast, 1981-84; AD 12.5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Office of Development, 1981-8/1983; AD 12.10.1 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 6/1981-8/1983; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - IBM, 3/1983-8/1983; AD 12.10.3/5-51 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-51)
  - Cecil and Ida Green Gift, 1980-8/1983; AD 12.10.3/5-52 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-52)
  - Prospective Donors, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - Beckman, 8/1982-8/1983; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - Foundations, Funds Misc., 9/1981-8/1983; AD 12.10.4 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Foundations, Funds Misc., 6/1982-8/1983; PAD 12.10.4 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.10.4)
  - Shell Co. Foundation, 10/1982-10/1983; AD 12.10.4/200 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.4/200)
  - Technology, Licensing/Patents and Copyrights, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 12.11 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.11)
  - Lands and Buildings, 10/1982-8/1983; AD 12.14 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Mellon Foundation, 9/1982-8/1983; PAD 12.14.4/139 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14.4/139)
  - Stanford Red Barn, 1982-8/1983; AD 12.14.7/9 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/9)